SUNNY JAIN

Senior Software Developer

- √ 7798844366 @ sunnyjain3023@gmail.com
- https://sunnyjain1008.github.io/
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/sunny-jain-729936147/
- ☆ April 25, 1995

SUMMARY

I'm a web developer and having 4 + experience who aims to combine the beauty of design with the logical perfection of coding. I train myself every day and push my own limits to discover new ways of creating a great experience for the users.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Senior Software Engineer

2022 - Present

PUNE

Tata Consultancy Services

- Working as System Engineer as a part of system engineer creating a beautiful front end designs for end user using React Js / TypeScript / Node Js.
- Designed and developed reusable software components which used in 3 different project with reducing development effort by 50%
- · Rated with the best annual performance rating for all the years during my stint

Software Developer

2020 - 2022

Dakshabhi IT Solution

PUNE

- At Dakshabhi IT Solution, we were at the forefront of innovative IT solutions, specializing in
 the development of cutting-edge web applications, mobile apps, and lonic framework
 expertise. Our team of seasoned professionals seamlessly blended creativity and technical
 prowess to deliver tailor-made solutions that not only met but exceeded our clients'
 expectations.
- Leveraging the latest technologies and best practices, we crafted responsive and userfriendly web applications that enhanced digital experiences.
- Our proficiency in the lonic framework allowed us to build cross-platform mobile apps with exceptional performance and a native-like feel.
- With a commitment to quality and client satisfaction, we transformed ideas into reality, ensuring our clients stayed ahead in the rapidly evolving digital landscape.

Junior Software Engineer

01/2019 - 06/2019

Nyati Technology Pvt.Lim,Pune

PUNE

- At Nyati Technology Pvt.Lim,our internship program offered a dynamic and immersive experience in the realm of web application development.
- As an intern with us, you had the opportunity to dive into real-world projects, gaining hands-on experience in designing, developing, and deploying web applications.
- Under the mentorship of seasoned professionals, you were exposed to the latest technologies and industry best practices.
- From front-end user interfaces to back-end functionalities, our internship provided a comprehensive understanding of the entire web development lifecycle.
- Joining our internship at Nyati Technology Pvt.Lim meant being part of a dynamic environment that fostered learning, growth, and a solid foundation for a successful career in web application development.

EDUCATION

05/2016 - 05/2019
Percentage: 60.18 %
01/2013 - 04/2016
Percentage: 62.80 %
2011 - 2013
Percentage: 55.50 %
2010 - 2011
Percentage: 76.00 %



ACHIEVEMENTS

Xcelerate Warrior

Milind Lakkad, Global Head TCS, For outstanding contribution to the organization

on The Spot Award

Milind Lakkad, Global Head TCS, For outstanding contribution to the organization

on The Spot Award

Milind Lakkad, Global Head TCS, For outstanding contribution to the organization

Cyber Security

IIT Hydrabad

SKILLS

UI Technologies

Node · React JS · HTML · mySQL · CSS

Programming Languages:

Java · Javascript

Operating Systems

Mac · Linux · Windows

IDE's

VS Code · Eclips

Version Control:

GIT · BigBucket

Project Management Tools

Jira

Other

AWS · Informatic (IICS) · Elastic ·

Kibana Logs

LANGUAGES

English	Advance
HINDI	Advance
	0
Gujrathi	Native
Marathi	Notivo
Maratrii	Native

PROJECTS

AREOSPACE MAINTAINCE SERVICES PLANS

TCS,Pune

Capturing Areo MSP real time usage data

- This project was we are providing a engines for rental and as per usage of engine hours we are calculate the usage and generate there invoice as per rate escalation.
- This application is created for maintain and capturing real time usage hours.
- User can fill the usage hours from application and after 4 Hrs. we can validated and generate a invoice as per rate escalation policy. User also pay this invoices from portal.
- This application has two roles one for ADMIN and one for user.
- Admin can access all data like Invoices Open / Closed / Rate / Contracts / DMR etc.

SOFTWARE UPLOAD

TCS. Pune

The Global Design Model for Software Upload Portal. This would help customers from all SBGs to have common upload process for software

- To have a common Software Upload business process across all the strategic business group(Honeywell).
- To De-commission all the redundant application and provide a common Storage Repository to host all the software's across all strategic business group(SBG).
- To Align with current Portal Service Architecture.

AERO TECHNICAL PUBLICATION

TCS,Pune

To manage the overall Tech Pub business process across all the strategic business group (SBG)

- Provide a common functionality to download the technical publication across all the strategic group(SBG).
- · De-commission all the redundant applications.
- Provide common Storage Repository to host all the technical publications across all strategic business group(SBG).

ECO - EFFICIENCY

TCS,Pune

Eco Efficiency is a two-dimensional metrics which measures both environmental impact(TEWI) & the financial impact (CAPEX & OPEX) of a commercial refrigeration architecture.

- Eco Efficiency is a tool used to calculate below two main factors of a commercial refrigeration architecture
- 1-The Environmental Impact (TEWI)
- 2- The Financial Impact (CAPEX & OPEX)

StackAxis [Android Application] (Most Affordable proxy Services)

Dakshabhi IT Solutions ,Pune

Stackaxis is one of the largest growing proxy service providers

Stackaxis is one of the largest growing proxy service providers. We provide the fastest 4G coverage proxy server. Our service includes speed and safety to your work. You can choose between metered and unmetered connections, depending on your choice. There is no limit on bandwidth in our service. By becoming the premium service member, you can access more than

2,000,000+ unique IP, which are billed per GB at affordable prices.

Patient Portal (Online Appointment Booking And Video Consultancy Mobile App)

Dakshabhi IT Solutions ,Pune

Online Appointment Booking And Video Consultancy Mobile App.

- Patient Portal is a Online Appointment Booking And Video Consultancy Mobile App. In app contains a online booking with doctor.
- In this app user can book appointment as per schedule time.
- This app contains following features like Video calling / Share Images / Chat with doctor and etc.

FIND ME ONLINE

git Github sunnyjain1008

in Linkedin sunny-jain-729936147

Portfolio
https://sunnyjain1008.github.io/

Instagram marvadichoro_

f Facebook

jainsunny10008

✓ X

_Sunny_Jain

INTERESTS

Travelling

Photography

Video Editing